const zenaDecks = [
    {
        deckName: 'Human Terms',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ],
        _id: '12'
    },
    {
        deckName: 'Meowza',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ],
        _id: '123'
    },
    {
        deckName: 'Purrfect',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ],
        _id: '1234'
    },
    {
        deckName: 'Favorite Walls',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ],
        _id: '1245'
    },
    {
        deckName: 'Sleeping Spots',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        deckName: 'Seth vs. Laura',
        cards: [
            {
                front: 'perfect baby',
                back: 'that\'s essentially just me, Zena'
            },
            {
                front: 'perfect baby move',
                back: 'basically any cute thing I do'
            },
            {
                front: 'wet chin',
                back: 'when I get a drink of water and my chin is super wet afterward'
            },
            {
                front: 'steam pile',
                back: 'when I take a big ol\' shitski'
            },
            {
                front: 'scritchie',
                back: 'that good-good scracth behind my ear'
            }
        ]
    },
];

export default zenaDecks;
